Guide to the Cornell University songs and sheet music, 1870-2000.
Cornell University songs and sheet music, 1870-2000.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University songs and sheet music, 1874-2000.
47-6-2124
Cornell University.
1.4 cubic ft.
Printed materials, publications
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell song books and sheet music.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Cornell song books. Booklets, and sheet music and other music and lyric sheets. A number of the songs are written by Cornell alumni and were performed by the Cornell Glee Club. Some of the items contain history or other information about the songs and their composers. Some tunes are Ithaca or locally related and others are not Cornell related, but standard college and university items. Includes, but not limited to: "Big Red Team," by Romeyn Berry, 1905, with picture of football team; "Carnelian and White," by K. L. Roberts and T. J. Lindorff, 1906; "Fight for Cornell," by K. L. Roberts and T. J. Lindorff, 1907; "We March to Victory," by G. F. Pond, 1908; "Cornell Victorious," by S. H. Ayer, 1915, with picture of Touchdown, the bear mascot; "My Old Cornell," by Will A. Dillon, n.d; Cornell drinking, Glee Club and sporting event songs, and others. Also some band music and musical program from the opening of Sage Chapel, June 13, 1875; Banquet Songs of XCI (Class of 1891?), February 15, 1889. There are multiple copies of some items.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Ayer, S. H., Jr.; Berry, Romeyn, 1881-1957.; Dillon, Will A.; Lindorff, T. J. (Theodore Julius).; Pond, G. F.; Roberts, Kenneth Lewis, 1885-1957.; Roberts, Kenneth Lewis, 1885-1957.; Cornell University -- Societies, etc.; Cornell University; Cornell University. Glee Club.; Cornell University. Banjo Club.; Cornell University. Mandolin Club.
Subjects:
Music -- New York (State) -- Ithaca -- Societies, etc.; Choral societies -- New York (State) -- Ithaca.; Students' songs -- United States.
Form and Genre Terms:
Sheet music.; Songs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
See also the Cornell University Glee Club Records, #37-6-2399, http://resolver.library.cornell.edu/cgi-bin/EADresolver?id=RMA02399.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Sheet Music
Series II. Song Books
Series III. Song Booklets
Series IV. Miscellaneous Lyric Sheets and Music Related Items
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Sheet Music
  - Hail Cornell, Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Lyrics and music by Albert W. Smith '78 and George F. Pond '10.
    Handwritten copy by Pond.
  - Photocopies of music, Undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Includes Give My Regards to Broadway, Varsity Drag, The Sweetheart of Sigma Chi, Whiffenpoof Song
  - When Day Is Done, Undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Not a Cornell song, no composer given. Blue copy music is marked L. M. N..
  - The Chimes, 1870 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Lyrics by Francis M. Finch. Music by W. O. Fiske.
  - Cascadilla Waltz, 1872 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Composed by Edward Bausch '74.
    Complements of the composer.
  - 1875, 1890 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Lyrics by John De Witt Warner '72. Music by Archibald C. Weeks '72.
  - Cornell Two-Step, 1895 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Composed by George O. Wagner, possibly George Olds Wagner '00.
    Dedicated to the Cornell University. Also includes a number of other non Cornell tunes from the Queen City Music Publishing Company.
  - Cornell Rowing Song, 1899 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Lyrics by Edward A. McCreary '00. Music by Edwin Haviland, Jr. '99 Grad.
    Dedicated to the Cornell Navy.
  - Cornell Alumni March and Two-Step, 1901; 3 copies (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Composed by Frederick B. Downing '94.
    Also includes the Rough Riders March, 1898
  - Eighty-four, 1904 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Lyrics by Henry Pelouze de Forest '84. Music is the British Grenadiers.
    Dedicated to the Class of '84 on their vigintennial, June 22, 1904.
  - The Big Red Team, 1905; 5 copies (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Lyrics by Romeyn Berry '04. Music by Charles E. Tourison '06
    One copy from the Frank Arthur Barton papers, one copy with the football players on the cover identified.
  - Cornell University Medley: March & Two Step, 1905 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Composed by H. A. Lyon, possibly Henry Adelbert Lyon Law '97.
    Dedicated to Jacob Gould Schurman.
  - Carnellian and White, 1906; 9 copies (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Lyrics by Kenneth L. Roberts '08. Music by Theodore J. Lindorff '07
    One copy from the Frank Arthur Barton papers.
  - Cheering, Cheering for Cornell, 1907; 7 copies (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Lyrics by Archibald C. Weeks '72. Music is the Air, Marching Through Georgia.
    Dedicated to the Pioneer Classes of Cornell University.
  - Field Song, 1907; 2 copies (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Composed by William Luton Wood
  - Fight for Cornell, 1907; 2 copies (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Goodbye, Cornell Goodbye, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Composed by William Haywood Wright.
    Signed by the composer to Captain Barton. From the Frank Arthur Barton papers.
  - We March to Victory, 1908; 3 copies (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Lyrics and music by George F. Pond '10
  - Cornell I Yell Cornell!, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Lyrics by Thomas Riggs Cox '11. Music by Harold Franklin Welch '10
  - Stand Up For Cornell, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Dedicated to Mr. Charles E. Courtney.
  - Fair Cornell, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Lyrics by James O. Winslow '11. Music by Edward F. Johnston.
    Waltzes. Dedicated to Harold MacDowell Brown.
  - Valse Lente, 1911 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Composed by J. Franklin Bradley '11.
    Inscribed by the composer to E.A. Richmond.
  - Cornell Reunion Song, 1914; 2 copies (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Lyrics by Henry Pelouze de Forest '84. Music by Jack Judge and Harry Williams.
    Dedicated to the Senior Class December 29, 1914.
  - The University Rag, 1914 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Composed by F. Frayser Hinton and Donald Stonebraker.
    Dedicated to the Cornell University Glee Club. Also includes Don't Let Me Sleep 'till My Dreams Come True by W. C. R. Hart and Wheatly Davis.
  - Cornell Victorious, 1915; 6 copies (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Lyrics and music by S. Hibbard Ayer Jr. '14
    Has a photo of Touchdown the bear on the cover.
  - Two Cornell Songs, 1915; 3 copies (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Includes '88 Class Song, lyrics by Albert E. Hoyt '88. Music by Charles W. Curtis '88 and Cheer for the Team, composed by Charles W. Curtis '88.
  - America's Message, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Lyrics by Harvey Worthington Loomis. Music by Arthur Edward Johnstone.
    Inspired by President Wilson's War address to Congress April 2, 1917.
  - Dear Land of Freedom, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Composed by Archibald C. Weeks '72
  - My Old Cornell, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Composed by Will A. Dillon.
    Dedicated to The Boys on the Hill.
- Series II. Song Books
  - College Songs, Undated (Box 1)
    Cover features what appears to be Roberts and Stone Halls.
    Includes: Alma Mater, Cornell, The Song Of The Classes, Evening Song At Cornell, The Chimes, The Call Of The Fields, Bustonian Chorus, There's A Wedding In The Orchard, In The Gloaming, The Old Farm At Cornell, Last Night, I Arise From Dreams Of Thee, Drink To Me Only With Thine Eyes, Juanita, The Quilting Party, Jingle, BElls, When First I Kissed Sweet Margaret, Sweet And Low, Annie Laurie, Here's To The Girl That I Love, Forsaken, The Loreley, Flow Gently, Sweet Afton, Jolly Boating Weather, Sailing, Soldier's Farewell, Nancy Lee, Old Black Joe, Old Folks At Home, My Bonnie, Down In Mobile, Nelly Was A Lady, The Two Roses, Darling Nelly Gray, How Can I Leave Thee!, Hard Times Come Again No More, Landlord, Fill The Flowing Bowl, Upidee, The Man Who Has Plenty Of Good Peanuts, Solomon Levi, The Pope, The Old Oaken Bucket, Home Again, Home, Sweet Home, Lead, Kindly Night, Rocked In The Cradle Of The Deep, The Star-Spangled Banner, Stars Of The Summer Night, The Red, White, And Blue, America, Battle Hymn Of The Republic, John Brown's Body, Maryland! My Maryland!, Dixie's Land, We're Tenting To-Night, The Watch On The Rhine, The Marseillaise, Round The Old Camp Fire, Old Nassau, Sans Souci, Our College Cheer, Auld Lang Syne, Good-Night, Ladies!.
  - Songs of Cornell, Undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Presented by the Sphinx Head Senior Honorary Society. Also includes a bit of history about each song. Includes Alma Mater by Archibald Croswell Weeks '72 and Wilmot Moses Smith '74. The words of the Cornell Alma Mater were written early in 1872, through mutual suggestion, by Weeks and Smith, who then occupied rooms in the old Woodruff block on Tioga Street.
    Cornell Victorious by S. Hibbard Ayer Jr. '14.
    Cornell, lyrics by George Kingsley Birge '72 to the tune 'Twas My Last Cigar. First published in the Cornell Era spring 1869.
    Song of the Classes by Frank A. Abbott '90.
    Give My Regards to Davy to the tune of Give My Regards to Broadway.
    Crew Song, lyrics by Robert James Kellog '91 and music by William Luton Wood. First published in the 1892 Cornellian.
    Alumni Song, lyrics by Louis Carl Ehle '90, music by Wiliam Luton Wood. First published in the 1893 Cornellian.
    Evening Song, lrycs by Henry Tyrrell '80, to the tune Tannenbaum. First published in the Cornell Era 1877.
  - Songs of Cornell, 1900 (Box 1)
    B. F. Lent Publisher
    Dedicated to Cornell's Athletes. Includes some text and the following songs: Alma Mater, Cornell, 1875: The Cornell Cheer, The Chimes, Alumni Song, Song Of The Classes, Rowing Song, Crew Song, Bustonian Chorus, Evening Song. (poor condition)
  - Songs of Cornell, 1903 (Box 1)
    Dedicated to Cornell's Athletes. Includes some text and the following songs: Alma Mater, Cornell, 1875: The Cornell Cheer, The Chimes, Alumni Song, Song Of The Classes, Rowing Song, Crew Song, Bustonian Chorus, Evening Song, Smoking Song, Boating Song.
  - College Songs No. 3, 1907 (Box 1)
    Includes various songs popular at colleges at the time, not Cornell specific. O Alma Mater, Aura Lee, Bavarian Yodel, Ching A Ling, Camptown Races, Emmett's Lullaby, Fill Up Your Stein, Forty Nine bottles, Go Down Moses, Good Night Ladies, Home Sweet Home, It's A Way We Have At Old Harvard, Lauriger Horatius, Little Brown Jug, A Little More Cider, My Meerschaum Pipe, Mary Had A Little Lamb, My Last Cigar, Mary And Martha, Old King Cole, Old Noah He Did Build An Ark, The Pope, Peter Gray, Rocked In The Cradle Of The Deep, Rio Grande, Swing Low Sweet Chariot, Tom Big Bee River, There Were Three Crows, Turn Back Pharoh's Army, There's Music In The Air, Three Little Pigs, Where Oh Where Is My Little Dog Gone, Where Oh Where, Where Are You Going My Pretty Maid.
  - Songs of Cornell, 1906 (Box 1)
    Dedicated to Cornell's Athletes. Includes some text and the following songs: Alma Mater, Cornell, 1875: The Cornell Cheer, The Chimes, Alumni Song, Song Of The Classes, Rowing Song, Crew Song, Bustonian Chorus, Evening Song, Smoking Song, Boating Song, Football Song (Big Red Team).
  - Songs of Cornell, Mixed Voices, 1907 (Box 1)
  - College Songs, 1909 (Box 1)
    Cover features Roberts and Stone Halls. Published by Hinds, Noble & Eldredge. Includes foreword by Liberty Hyde Bailey.
    Includes Cornell Songs: All Round The World, Alma Mater, The Big Red Team or The Foot-Ball Song, Bustonian Chorus, The Call Of The Fields, Carnelian And White, The Chimes, Cornell, Dreaming, 1875: The Cornell Cheer, Evening Song, Fight For Cornell, Isle Of Delight, Locomotive Yell, The Old Farm At Cornell, Short Yell, The Song Of The Classes, Yells.
    Songs of Other Colleges: Alma Mater – Amherst, Alma Mater – University of Chicago, Cheer For Old Amherst, Dear Old Yale, Fair Harvard, Hail, Pennsylvania!, Old Nassau, Orange And The Black, Our College Cheer, Sans Souci, We Stand By Our Classes, The Yellow And The Blue.
    Humorous Songs: Broke! Broke! Broke!, The Bull-Dog, Change of the Short Ags, Doctor Peter Price’s Permanent Panacea, The Dutch Company, He Was Nervous, I Wish You’d Shave, Nut Brown Maiden, A Parody Song, Poor Ned, Where, O Where?.
    Popular College Songs: Am I Not Fondly Thine Own?, Annie Laurie, Auld Lang Syne, Ben Bolt, A College Medley, Down In Mobile, Drinking Song, Drink To Me Only With Thine Eyes, Forsaken, Good-night, Ladies!, Here’s To The Girl That I Love, Home, Sweet Home, How Can I Leave Thee?, I Arise From The Dreams Of Thee, Jolly Boating Weather, Juanita, Last Night, Love’s Old Sweet Song, Maid Of Athens, Massa’s In De Cold Ground, My Bonnie, My Old Kentucky Home, Nelly Was A Lady, Old Folks At Home, The Old Oaken Bucket, Over The Banister, The Quilting Party, Romeo And Juliet, Soldier’s Farewell, Stars Of The Summer Night, Sweet And Low, Sweetheart, I Wait For Thee, Take My Love To Rosalie, There’s Music In The Aid, The Two Roses, WE Meet Again To-night.
    Patriot And Sacred Songs: America, Battle Hymn of The Republic, Dixie;s Land, Jerusalem The Golden, John Brown’s Body, Lead, Kindly Light, The Marseillaise, Maryland!, My Maryland!, Old Black Joe, The Red White, and Blue, Russian Hymn, The Star-Spangled Banner, The Watch On The Rhine, We’re Tenting To-night.
  - Songs of Cornell, 1909 (Box 1)
    Dedicated to Cornell's Athletes. Includes some text and the following songs: Alma Mater, Cornell, 1875: The Cornell Cheer, The Chimes, Alumni Song, Song Of The Classes, Rowing Song, Crew Song, Bustonian Chorus, Evening Song, Smoking Song, Boating Song, Big Red Team, Fight For Cornell, Carnelian And White.
  - Cornell Songs, 1914 (Box 1)
    Published and compiled by the Board of Editors at the authorization of the Agricultural Association of the New York State College of Agriculture at Cornell University. Published by Hinds, Noble, & Eldredge. Includes forward by Liberty Hyde Bailey.
    Includes: All 'Round The World, Cornell, Alma Mater, Annie Laurie, Auld Lang Syne, The Big Red Team, Bingo, Blow Ye Winds, Heigh-ho!, Boating Song, Bring The Wagon Home, John, The Bull-Dog, Bustonian Chorus, Carnelian And White, The Chimes, Cornell, Crew Song, Dear Evelina, Sweet Evelina, Dear Old Pals, Dixie Land, Down In Mobile, Dreaming, Drink To Me Only With Thine Eyes, The Dutch Company, 1875-The Cornell Cheer, Evening Song, Fight For Cornell, Germany-Land, Give My Regards To Davy, Good-night, Ladies!, A Health To All Good Fellow, I Arise From Dreams Of Thee, Isle Of Delight, Jingle Bells, Juanita, Last Night, Levee Song, The Little Old Red Shaw, Long Live Our College, Love's Old Sweet Song, Meerschaum Pipe, The Mermaid, The Midshipmite, My Old Kentucky Home, Nelly Was A Lady, Noah, Old Black Joe, Old College Chum, Old Folks At Home, One, Two, Three, Four, On The Chapel Steps, Over The Banister, The Pope, The Poughkeepsie Races, The Quilting Party, Santa Lucia, Song Of The Classes, Spanish Cavalier, Stars Of A Summer Night, Sweet And Low, Sweetheart, I Wait For Thee, There's Music In The Air, Upon The College Campus, We Meet Again Tonight, We Stand By Our Classes, When First I Kissed Sweet Margaret, Where, Oh Where, Yells, Campus Song (University of Rochester, Cheer For Old Amherst, Down The Field (Yale), Fair Harvard, The Genesse (University of Rochester), Hail! Pennsylvania, Hamilton's Song, Oh! Syracuse, Old Nassau (Princeton), The Orange And The Black (Princeton), The Royal Purple (Williams), Sans Souci (Columbia), The Victors (Michigan), Yale Boola Song, The Yellow And Blue (Michigan).
  - Cornell Songs, 1915 (Box 1)
    Some different songs than the 1914 edition. Published and compiled by the Board of Editors at the authorization of the Agricultural Association of the New York State College of Agriculture at Cornell University. Published by Hinds, Noble, & Eldredge. Includes forward by Liberty Hyde Bailey.
    Includes: All 'Round The World, Cornell, Alma Mater, Alumni Song, And When I Die, At Eight Upon The Hill, Auld Lang Syne, Australia, The Big Red Team or The Foot-Ball Song, Blow Ye Winds, Heigh-ho!, Boating Song, Bring The Wagon Home, John, Bustonian Chorus, By The Watermelon Vine, Lindy Lou, Carnelian And White, Carry Me Back To Old Virginny, Castle On The Nile, Cheer For The Team, The Chimes, Co-Eds' Chant, Cornell, Cornell Hymn, Cornellio, Cornell Yells, Crew Song, Dear Old Pals, Dixie's Land, Down By The Steam (Rebecca), Down In Mobile, Dreaming, Drink To Me Only With Thine Eyes, 1875-The Cornell Cheer, Eli, Evening Song, Everybody Works But Davy, Faculty, Fight For Cornell, Forty-Nine Bottles, Founder's Centenary Hymn, Founder's Hymn, Germany-Land, The Girls of Ithaca, Give My Regards To Davy, Glorious Mother-Cornell, Good-night, Ladies!, H-e-r-p-i-c-i-de, Honey, Dat I Love So Well, Isle Of Delight, Jingle Bells, Juanita, The King Of The Cannibal Islands, Last Night, Levee Song, The Little Old Red Shaw, The Midshipmite, Moon, Moon, My Old Kentucky Home, Old Black Joe, Old College Chum, Old Folks At Home, One, Two, Three, Four, On The Chapel Steps, The Poughkeepsie Races, Rocked In The Cradle Of The Deep, Rowing Song, Sage Maidens, Santa Lucia, Senior, Junior, Soph., Frosh., Soldier's Farewell, The Song Of The Classes, Spanish Cavalier, Stars Of A Summer Night, Sweetheart, I Wait For Thee, Tell Me, Maiden, Upon The College Campus, Campus Song (University of Rochester, Cheer For Old Amherst, Down The Field (Yale), Fair Harvard, The Genesse (University of Rochester), Hail! Pennsylvania, Hamilton's Song, Oh! Syracuse, Old Nassau (Princeton), The Orange And The Black (Princeton), Our Director (Harvard), The Princeton Cannon Song March, The Royal Purple (Williams), Yale Boola Song, The Yellow And Blue (Michigan).
  - Cornell Songs, 1915 (Box 1)
    Slightly different publisher than the other 1915 edition. Published and compiled by the Board of Editors at the authorization of the Agricultural Association of the New York State College of Agriculture at Cornell University. Published by Hinds, Hayden, & Eldredge. Includes forward by Liberty Hyde Bailey.
  - Songs of Cornell, 1940 (Box 1)
    Compiled and Edited by Paul J. Weaver, published by the Cornell Alumni Association.
    Includes: All 'Round the World, Cornell, Alma Mater, Alumnae Song, Alumni Song, The Big Red Team, Boating Song, Bustonian Chorus, Carneilian And White, The Chimes, Cornell, Cornell Changes (Jenny McGraw Rag) Cornell Hymn, Cornell Victorious, Crew Song, Dreaming, 1875, Evening Song, Everybody Works But Davy, Faculty, Fight For Cornell, Give My Regards To Davy, Hail Thou In Majesty, Cornell, The Hill, In The Red And The White, The Isle Of Delight, Lingering, Loyal Daughters Of Cornell, March On, Cornell, Tales Of Old Cornell, One, Two, Three, Four, The Poughkeepsie Course, In The Red And The White, Rowing Song, The Senior Dirge, Senior, Junior, Soph'more, Frosh, Song For Cornell, Song Of The Classes, Song Of The Classes (Women's Version), Tales of Old Cornell
  - Songs of Cornell, 1948 (Box 1)
  - Songs of Cornell, 1988 (Box 1)
    Compiled and Edited by Thomas A. Sokol. Published by the Cornell University Glee Club. Includes multiple voice part arrangements of the songs.
    Includes: Alma Mater, Alumni Song, The Big Red Team, Carnelian And White, The Chimes, Cornell, Cornell Champions, Cornell Changes, Cornell Hymn, Cornell Victorious, Crew Song, 1875, Evening Song, Fight For Cornell, Gaudeamus Igitur, Give My Regards To Davy, Hail Thou In Majesty, Cornell, The Hill, In The Red And The White, March On, Cornell, My Old Cornell, New Cornell Fight Song, Song FOr Cornell, Song Of The Classes, Strike Up A Song To Cornell, Tales Of Old Cornell.
- Series III. Song Booklets
  These contain lyrics only, no music. Song order and spellings are as they appear in the booklets.
  - Cornell Songs, Undated; Brochure sized with red crest containing the title. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Includes: Alma Mater, Cornell, Evening Song, The Chimes, Alumni Song, Crew Song, Cornell Victorious, Poughkeepsie Course, Carnelian And White, Fight For Cornell, The Big, Red Team, Song Of The Classes, Here's To Old Cornell, I Want To BE A Mormon, Bustonian Chorus, Give My Regards To Davy, Levee Song, Noah, Push The Damper In, Dip Me In The Golden Sea, Honey, One, Two, Three, Four, I Had A Dream, Dear, That's Where My Money Goes, Ma Honey, Hindoostan, Newsy's Song, I'm A Little Prarie Flower, Ma Tildy Ann, The Pope, Landlord, Fill The Flowing Bowl, Li'l Liza Jane, 'Round Her Neck She Wears A Yeller Ribbon, Bring Back My Bonnie To Me, The Bull Dog, Little Pig, Caisson Song, Drunk Last Night, I Want To Be A Bar Keep, My CAttle On The Sunny River Nile, Pack Up Your Troubles In Your Old Kit Bag, Sweet Adeline, Goodnight, My Love, Good-night, Ladies.
  - Cornell Songs as Sung by the Northeastern Ohio Cornell Association of Cleveland, Undated; Teal cover (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Includes: Alma Mater, Evening Song, Cornell, The Chimes, The Cornell Cheer (1875, Alumni Song, Cornell Rowing Song, Here's To Old Cornell, CornellBoating Song, Kindling Wood, Crew Song, Big Red Team, Song Of The Classes, Carnelian And White.
  - Cornell Songs as Sung by the Northeastern Ohio Cornell Association of Cleveland, Undated; Brown cover (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Includes: Alma Mater, Evening Song, Cornell, The Chimes, The Cornell Cheer (1875, Alumni Song, Cornell Rowing Song, Here's To Old Cornell, CornellBoating Song, Kindling Wood, Crew Song, Big Red Team, Song Of The Classes, Carnelian And White, Bustonian Chorus, What You Going To Do?, Regards To Davy, Faculty, Everybody Works But Father, Stein Song, Australia!, Anheuser Bush, Stein Song (Prince of Pilsen), Landlord, Fill The Flowing Bowl, Am I The Boss?, Push The Damper In, Honey, Levee Song.
  - Cornell Songs, Twenty-Third Annual Dinner of Cornell Alumni in New York City and Vicinity, Undated; 2 copies (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Includes: Alma Mater, Cornell, The Chimes, 1875, Alumni Song, Song Of The Classes, Crew Song, Rowing Song, Bustonian Chorus, Cornell Evening Song, We Mett Again To-night, The Pope, Mermaid, There Is A Tavern In The Town, The Stein Song, Drinking-song, Give Us A Drink, I've Been Working On The LEvee, Bring The Wagon Home, Kindling-wood, In The evening By The Moonlight, Strolling, I Used To KNow A Little Yellow Girl, Far Away In The South.
  - Songs of Cornell, Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Light tan cover. Published by the Corner Bookstores. Has photographs of the Corner Bookstore, Triangle Branch Store, and information about their products.
    Includes: Alma Mater, Cornell, 1875: - The Cornell Cheer, The Chimes, Alumni Song, Song Of The Classes, Cornell Rowing Song, Crew Song, Bustonian Chorus, Cornell Boating Song, The Big Red Team, Evening Song.
  - Songs of Cornell, Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Dark tan cover. Taylor & Company. Published by the Corner Bookstores. Has photographs of the Corner Bookstore, Triangle Branch Store, and information about their products.
  - Cornell University Songs, 1881; 2 copies (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Compiled by L. And H. Published by Andrus & Church. Only Authorized Edition.